Do you have a hobby that helps you relax and unwind?
你有能帮助自己放松的爱好吗？
For some people, there is no better way to switch off than spending time in the garden.
对一些人来说，没有什么比在花园里度过时光更好的放松方式了。
This small private area of green space can be their oasis of calm.
这片小小的私人绿地可以成为他们心灵的宁静绿洲。
It's no wonder some of us turn to gardening as a form of therapy.
难怪我们中的一些人求助于园艺来作为一种心理治疗方式。
A survey conducted by the Royal Horticultural Society, found that 82% of people in the UK said that gardening makes them happier.
英国皇家园艺学会进行的一项调查发现，82%的英国人表示园艺让他们更快乐。
It also found that 70% of them, given the choice, would prefer to spend their working day in the garden with just 9% opting for an office.
调查还发现，70%的人如果可以选择，更愿意在花园里度过工作日，而只有9%的人选择在办公室工作。
For those with green fingers, the pleasure of gardening comes from getting out in the fresh air, in all weathers and communing with nature - even if there are a few too many creepy-crawlies!
对于那些有园艺天赋的人来说，园艺的乐趣来自于来到户外在各种天气情况下呼吸新鲜空气，与大自然交流——即使有太多恐怖的小爬虫！
It can also be seen as a sort of digital-detox - time away from technology.
它也可以被视为一种数字排毒——远离科技的时光。
Some experts actually believe that getting outside to dig and plant things acts as a 'natural high'.
实际上，一些专家认为，到户外挖土和种植植物会让人产生一种“天然的快感”。
Dr Christopher Lowry, a neuroscientist at the University of Colorado, injected a bacterium commonly found in soil into mice to see what effect this would have on them.
科罗拉多大学的神经学家克里斯托弗·洛瑞博士将一种常见于土壤中的细菌注射到老鼠体内，看看这会对它们产生什么影响。
He found the bacterium had a similar effect on the mice as an antidepressant drug might.
他发现这种细菌对老鼠的影响与抗抑郁药物可能产生的影响类似。
When we dig in soil we ingest this bacterium through our lungs or cuts in our skin so Dr Lowry concluded that since the mice seemed happier when treated with soil bacteria, it's likely we would be too.
当我们在土壤中挖掘时，我们会通过肺部或皮肤上的伤口摄入这种细菌，所以洛瑞博士得出结论，既然接触过土壤细菌的老鼠似乎更快乐，那么我们很可能也是如此。
Garden can also be used as a way of treating addiction.
园艺也可以作为一种治疗成瘾的方法。
There's evidence that recovering alcoholics who have been given the opportunity to plant, grow, and even sell their produce, have managed to stop their addictive habits.
有证据表明，那些有机会种植、培育甚至出售自己农产品的戒酒者，已经成功戒掉了成瘾的习惯。
Scot Stephenson, for example, got expelled from school and started a vocational qualification in gardening.
例如，苏格兰人斯科特·斯蒂芬森被学校开除后，开始学习园艺方面的职业资格课程。
He says "I got my NVQ level 2 which is my first qualification and enjoyed it ever since."
他说：“我获得了国家职业资格二级证书，这是我的第一个资格证书，从那以后我就一直很享受园艺。”
Whatever the reason, there are many therapeutic benefits to getting your hands dirty, doing some physical hard work and then watching your garden grow.
不管是什么原因，弄脏双手，做一些体力劳动，然后看着自己的花园成长，这有许多治疗性的益处。
Does this sound like your idea of fun?
这听起来像是你所认为的乐趣吗？